我们要不要再过一遍
All right, should we run through it one more time?
好  目标是贝塞拉兄弟
All right. The targets are the Becerra Brothers,
恩里克和赫克托
Enrique and Hector.
拉丁毒贩
Latin Players.
从这俩人手里买三次了
Bought from these guys three times,
所以应该不难
so it should be nice and easy.
九千应该能买到第八包
Nine grand gets us that eighth.
我们去买货  告诉你们位置
We'll make the exchange, give you guys the positive,
然后抓人  午饭前就能收监
and then take 'em down, book 'em before lunch.
好  但是有个问题
Yeah, one problem.
-你看起来像大力士保罗  -我就是想穿成那样
- You look like Paul Bunyan. - That's what I was going for.
保罗是个帅气的大高个  多谢夸奖
Paul Bunyan was a handsome giant, so thank you.
之前在公园遇到玛凯拉挺开心的
Cool seeing Makayla at the park the other day.
看她笑起来真好
Good to see her laugh.
是啊  她是我见过最坚强的人  凯文
Yeah. She's the strongest person I know, Kev.
那你呢  毕竟你收留了她
You? Well, you brought her in.
这可是个不小的挑战
That's a big challenge.
我很享受  真的
Yeah, I love it. I really do.
-超享受  -可是
- I love it. - And?
可是我晚上几乎没力气爬上床
And, um, I can barely crawl into bed at the end of the day
而那还是在情况算顺利的情况下
and that's when everything goes perfect.
多双手帮你  是不是会好一些
Probably wouldn't hurt to have another pair of hands,
你说呢
would it?
你想过让鲁塞克参与进来吗
Thought about wrapping Ruz into this?
-想过  -然后呢
- Yeah, I have. - And?
-气色不错  -开始了
- Yo, looks good. - Here we go.
-开始了  -你们好啊
- Here we go. - What's up, fellas?
你好吗  兄弟
How do? What's up, bro?
-在这里住得挺舒服吧  -谁不是呢
- Living the dream over here. - Ain't we all?
来看看吧  整整九千
A'ight, check it out. That's 9 large.
需要的话可以数一数
You can count it if you got to.
不用了  我去拿货
All good. I'll get your package.
马上来
Right on.
你们要尝尝味道吗
Y'all need a taste of the product?
不用了  问题不大
Nah, man. We're good, we're good.
我们一个兄弟跟我说
One of our boys called us,
他上次抽这个都上头了
said he was in the shoulder with this stuff last time.
是啊
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
我们的东西纯得很
Yeah, we got that good stuff, man.
是啊
Right on.
我们可不是闹着玩的
Come on. We don't play around.
我知道
I know.
跟上次的配方一样吧
It's the same recipe as last time, right?
-绝对的  -绝对够纯  兄弟
- Tried and true. - Purity, homey.
所以结晶才会这么大
It's why the crystals are so big.
我知道  这就是我要的
Oh, I know. That's what I'm talking about.
那来吧
All right, let's do this.
杰  趴下
Jay, get down!
走
Let's go.
5021E  呼叫指挥中心  有人向警员开枪
5021 Eddie, 10-1, 10-1! Shots fired at the police!
我们在南贾斯汀街区4200号
We're at the 4200 block of South Justine.
有卧底警员遭到开火
We got undercover officers taking fire.
5021E  是否有警员中枪
Eddie, are there officers hit?
未知  正在赶往现场
Unknown. Approaching now.
所有人员注意  有警员需要支援
All again, we have a 10-1 being called.
杰  亚当
Jay, Adam!
我们没事  我们没事
Guys, we're okay! We're good!
枪手乘坐银色车辆向南侧逃窜
Shooter's in a silver pickup fleeing southbound.
5021D  警员未中枪
5021 David, officers are not hit.
我重复  警员没有中枪
I repeat, officers are not hit.
开枪者乘坐银色车辆在贾斯汀路逃往南侧
Offenders fled southbound on Justine in a silver pickup.
刚才是怎么回事
What the hell just happened?
芝加哥警署  第八季第七集
情况如何
All right. So where are we?
我拍到了逃逸车辆的部分照片
I got a partial from the shooter's vehicle that fled southbound.
公共信息中心正在搜查
CPIC's running it down.
是一辆比较新款的西维拉多
A newer-model Silverado.
-有弹壳吗  -目前有19颗
- Any shell casings? - 19 so far.
够了
That'll do.
突击步枪  绿色弹头  口径0.223
Assault rifle. Green tip .223s.
好的
All right.
让鉴证科包起来  贴标签  亲自送往弹道科
Have Forensic bag, tag, hand-deliver 'em to Ballistics.
我们知道这两名死者
Well, we know these two victims
是搞帮派的冰毒贩子
are gang-affiliated meth dealers,
去街头找线索
so hit the streets.
任何不和  定期枪击活动  都要查清楚
Look for beefs, anniversary shootings, all of it.
拿到警方监控  安保录像
Get me PODs, ShotSpotters.
不管是谁  差点干掉了我们自己两个兄弟
Hey, whoever did this damn near took out two of our own.
别忘了这一点
Don't forget that.
这是最近的安保摄像头了
Closest ShotSpotter to the shooting.
看来是有人先来的
Looks like someone else got there first.
这是23点的录像
It's from 2300 hours.
也就是出事前一晚
That's the night before it went down.
这说明这次枪击是有计划有组织的
Well, tells the shooting was calculated, planned.
-还有什么线索  -没什么值得行动的
- What else you got? - Nothing actionable.
我跟受害者的组织聊了聊
I talked to some of the victims' people.
他们不知道发生了什么  也不知道是谁
They say they don't know what's going on or who did this.
好  枪手的车有消息吗
Okay. Anything on the shooter's car?
警务信息中心从失窃报案记录上推断出车牌号
CPIC pieced together the plate from the hot sheet.
车辆是三天前失窃的
Vehicle was stolen three days ago.
我们登记要发协查通告  但...
We lodged BOLOs, but--
不  到现在车早就烧没了
No, vehicle's torched to the rims by now.
我们是在做无用功
We're circling the drain here.
实际上  可能也没有  警长
Actually, maybe not, Sarge.
组织犯罪技术部破解了
OCD busted into two burners
从贝塞拉兄弟家发现的两部一次性手机
found at the Becerra Brothers' place.
这些是手机上的短信
These are the texts on their phones.
"你敢卖就死定了"  "我警告过你"
"You sell, you die." "I warned you."
"死亡"  西班牙语
"Muerte." Dead.
有十来条
There's dozens of 'em.
有人威胁如果贝塞拉兄弟
Someone threatened to kill the Becerra Brothers
不退出冰毒生意就杀死他们
if they didn't get out of the meth game
然后他们就兑现这个威胁了
and then they made good on it.
-我们能追踪短信来源吗  -查不到某个人
- Okay, can we trace the texts? - Not to a person.
短信是在一次性手机之间发送的
Texts were sent burner-to-burner.
但要查出发送的区域  是可以的
But to a neighborhood? Yes.
组织犯罪技术部定位到加菲尔德公园一带
OCD puts them in and around Garfield Park.
我最好的线人之一汤米·雷恩
Yeah, one of my best CIs, Tommy Lane,
他是在加菲尔德公园卖冰毒的
he's a meth guy in Garfield Park.
-去找他一趟吧  -好
- Pay him a visit. - All right.
逗我玩呢吧
You gotta be kidding me.
当然了
Course.
-是他吗  -对  是他
- Is that him? - Yeah, that's him.
你们干嘛要来折腾我
Why are you busting my chops?
我一直都是这么干的
This is what I always do.
冷静  我只是问你  不是说是你干的
Calm down. I'm asking, not accusing.
你们跑到我家
Okay, this is me calm when you come to my home
就因为我找点乐子来兴师问罪
for the crime of having a good time
生日快乐  芬恩
还说我是小偷  还要我怎么冷静
and then call me a thief while you're at it.
我偷过的唯一的东西是我老婆的心
Only thing I ever stole was my old lady's heart.
天啊  汤米
God, Tommy.
他们应该因为你是个傻缺把你逮进去
They should take you to jail for being a stupid sap.
我有罪  我的女王  我因为爱你而有罪
I'm guilty, my queen. I am guilty of love.
我爱你
I love you. Okay?
-少来吧  -汤米
- Stop it. - Tommy.
-鲁塞  怎么样啊  兄弟  -你好吗
- Ruz, what's up, bro? - How you doing?
我们能私下说句话吗
Guys, speak to you privately real quick?
对  慢走不送啊
Yeah. Please take care.
-你待着别动  -我能去哪儿
- You stay there. - Where am I going?
-事儿还没完呢  -这是我的房子  我的家
- We ain't done with you. - My house, my home.
-汤米  -怎么了
- Tommy. - What?
我们找这个人有事
We got business with this guy.
-这个傻叉吗  -我明白
- With this nitwit? - Yeah, I know.
是看着不太可能
It seems improbable.
原创翻译  双语字幕
但到底是什么情况啊
But, uh, you wanna tell us what's going on?
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
出了什么问题
What's the problem?
你的人给他的孩子过生日
Look, your boy's having a birthday party for his kid.
翻译     青椒   nemonini
大人们都有点喝多了
The adults got a little wasted, all right?
邻居报警说太吵了
Neighbors called in a noise complaint.
-就这个  -不是  还有呢
- That's it? - No, that ain't it.
翻译     哈里不是波特   Carolgcz
我们有理由相信你朋友偷了这个充气屋
We got reason to believe your boy stole this bouncy house.
翻译     焦原   苏葵*5
这样吧
All right.
校对     苏葵
给我们个面子
Look, guys. Do us a favor.
撤吧  我们保证
Walk away, I promise you
会让这个傻叉不折腾了
we'll get this nitwit to shut things down, okay?
时间轴     chance-coco  西·查  Jenny
我保证
Promise.
别让他们再喝了
Take the tap off that keg?
好
Yes.
下次我们可不会撤了
We ain't walking away a second time.
后期     8T
合情合理
Fair enough.
听着
And hey, listen.
回头你们的更衣柜里应该有瓶装  棕色
Expect to find something bottled, brown,
总监     苏葵
还比较贵的东西
and moderately expensive in your lockers, okay?
非常感谢
I really appreciate it.
谢谢  谢谢
Thank you, thank you.
好说
We'll be fine.
鲁塞
Ruz.
你是真的脑子出毛病了吗  兄弟
Are you literally out of your mind, bro?
这么久了你跑哪儿去了  兄弟
Where you been all my life, bro?
现在还让你自己挑搭档呢啊
Still letting you pick your own partners these days, huh?
有时吧
Sometimes.
-脊梁发凉啊  -不会  熟了就好了
- Feel a chill. - Nah, she warms up.
别担心  来吧
Don't worry about it. Come on.
伊莎贝尔
Isabel!
来乐呵乐呵吧  来两口
Come party, man. Get a couple of shots!
-谢了  小家伙  -不客气
- Thanks, little man. - You're welcome.
来吧
All right, come on.
爸爸一会儿就出来
Dad will be back out in a minute.
-好的  -谢谢  伊莎贝尔
- Okay. - Thanks, Isabel.
那充气屋真是偷的
Really steal the bouncy house?
那还用说
Course I stole the bouncy house.
邻居真混球  芬恩玩得挺高兴的
Neighbor's a prick. Finn's having a good time.
上帝宁愿让你做贼也不愿意让你做混球
God would rather you be a thief than a prick any day.
-所以  -所以
- So. - So.
什么事
What's up?
我想让你做回老本行
I need you back in play.
-不是吧  -听着  哥们
- Come on. - Look, bro.
有些真正的恶人
We got a real bad person or persons
惹了很多严重麻烦
causing a lot of serious trouble.
有多严重
How serious?
有两个人  是两兄弟
Well, we got two men, brothers.
新城的冰毒贩子
Glass dealers in New City.
他们昨天都被枪杀了
They were both shot and killed yesterday
我们要查出
and we're trying to figure out
谁要抢他们的地盘
who's trying to muscle in on their turf
免得更多的人被杀
before more people get killed.
拜托  哥们  我现在的任务是
Come on, man. I'm doing this now, you know?
-生日蛋糕  充气房子  -我知道  我明白
- Birthday cakes, bouncy houses. - I know, I know, I get it.
不  你不明白哥们  我妻子伊莎贝尔信任我
No, you can't bro. My wife, Isabel, trust me.
要是别的女人早就走了
Lot of ladies would've left by now.
我已经尽力了  好吗
I pushed things far as I can go, all right?
我努力戒毒  不再吸了  你懂吗
I'm trying to get clean, get off the pipe, you know?
离开原来的一切
Got out of that whole scene.
我很敬佩你的所作所为
I got nothing but respect for that.
所以考虑一下
So check it:
我可以给你五千块
I can get you 5 grand
并让州检察官封存你的案底
and the state's attorney's gonna seal your record.
这意味着你不用再向任何潜在的雇主
That means you don't have to disclose anything
透露任何事
to any potential employers.
你只要做好这件事
You can do this whole thing right.
就可以找到份靠谱的工作  养家糊口
You can get a real job, raise your family.
好  但我要先跟伊莎贝尔谈谈
All right, but yo, I gotta talk to Isabel first.
她已经同意了  我们来之前给她打过电话
Well, she's already on board. Called her before we came over.
他挺狡猾的  对吗
He's conniving, ain't he?
我们称之为有说服力
Eh. Let's call it persuasive.
好吧  你真正要找的人是罗根
All right, the person you really want is Logan.
-谁  -罗根·蒂格
- Who? - Logan Teague.
他和我曾一起在那个街区贩毒
Me and him used to run around the block a few times.
就像我说的  我已经金盆洗手了
Like I said, I'm out of the game,
但罗根还在干
but Logan's a player.
他认识那里的所有人  他会
Knows everyone out there. He'll--
他会带我们去我们要去的地方
he'll take us where we need to go.
-好  -好
- Okay. - Nice.
食品酒水店
好
All right.
我先联系他一下
Hitting him up now.
你准备好了吗  没吸吧
Hey, you ready? You clean?
一点没有  像口哨一样
As a whistle.
我们怎么会用口哨来衡量
How did a whistle become the thing we use
人们干不干净
to measure being clean?
里面全是人们的口水
Got people's saliva all up in there.
用口哨的都是什么人
Who uses a whistle, huh?
-健身教练  警察  -好了
- Gym teachers? Cops? - All right, yo.
我们现在得正经点  好吗
Hey, we gotta be serious now, okay?
这是来真的
This is real.
嗯  也不算真的
Yeah, literally not real.
而且他们说讽刺已死
And they said irony was dead.
等等  我们到那时
Wait, what's your name supposed to be again
应该叫你什么来着
when we get over there?
-是迈克  哥们  -迈克
- It's Mike, bro. - Mike.
我说完了
I rest my case.
汤米  你会记得的  对吗
Tommy, you're gonna remember that, right?
亚当这次找了个话痨
Adam's got himself a live one.
没错
Indeed.
迈克跟单车押韵  迈克  单车  迈克  单车
Mike rhymes with bike. Mike, bike, Mike, bike.
对  好  我们进去时
Yeah, right. When we get in there,
你别做得太过
you don't gotta take it too far.
也不用刻意装作要做回本行
You don't gotta front like you're back in the game.
好  好
Right, right.
你只要把我介绍给他
You're just making introductions.
感觉像是为了我才跟罗根·蒂格见面
Felt like a meet would be good for me, Logan Teague,
你只要尝尝他的货  接下来的事
you get a little taste, and then after that,
你就不太擅长了
you gotta do what you're not so good at.
你要闭上你的臭嘴  让我跟他谈  好吗
Shut the hell up and let me do the talking, all right?
好  我一个字都不说  迈克
Kay. Mum's the word, Mikey.
好  然后我会准备交易
All right, so then I'll lay groundwork for a buy.
好  好
Cool, cool.
-就是这里吗  -对
- This it right here? - Yep.
开始了
Here we go.
-罗根  -汤米
- Hey, Logan. - Tommy, hey.
好啊  哥们
What's up, man?
我跟你说起过的兄弟迈克
My boy Mike I was telling you about.
已确认联系上罗根·蒂格
Contact confirmed with Logan Teague.
收到
Copy.
-这是给我的吗  -对
- Is that for me? - Yeah.
我们出去玩的时候抽
Smoke on up while we're hanging out.
-真的吗  -对  为了客户忠诚度
- For real? - Yeah, customer loyalty, eh?
哥们
Oh, dude.
我们一起做了多久生意了
How long we been running together?
我说过我爱你吗  哥们
I ever tell you I love you, man?
-永远都听不够  -我爱你
- Never enough. - I love you.
这个
This.
美上天了  美上天了
Sweet, sweet Jesus. Sweet, sweet Jesus.
杰  注意我们的线人正在嗑药
Jay, be advised our CI is using.
这随时都可能出问题
This could crap out at any second.
我知道你现在有点麻烦
I understand you're in a bit of a pickle.
你什么意思
What do you mean?
怎么  汤米没告诉你他给我打过电话
What, Tommy didn't tell you he called me and...
跟我说了你的问题
gave me a heads-up on your issues?
-他没跟我说  -汤米
- He did not, no. - Tommy.
你跟人一起做生意
You gotta tell people when you're, you know,
情况得告诉他们
sharing their business.
是  抱歉  你说的没错
Oh, yeah, sorry. That's right.
这家伙啊
This guy, eh?
这家伙真是
Yeah, this guy.
不是  我跟罗根说  你和我
Yeah, no, no. I told Logan how, you know you and me,
我们一起开始干这活
we're all in this new thing together.
是搭档
Partners, you know?
把货拿去郊区卖
Moving product up from the suburbs.
没错
Ah, that's right.
事情就是这样  伙计  我还跟他说...
This is what's up, man. I also told him...
我们的供货出了点问题
about our little supply problem, you know,
那些玩家们  墨西哥人
how the Mexicans, the Players, you know,
前几天挨了枪子儿  吓得要死
are scared as hell after getting shot up the other day.
伙计  我们不需要知道发生了什么  好吗
And look, man, we don't need to know what's up, all right?
这不是我们该管的事
It's above our pay grade.
我们需要知道的是
But we do need to know what's down
我们需要一个新的供货商
as in we need a new supplier.
这就是最重要的  伙计
I mean, that's about the long and short of it, man.
你们说的是贝塞拉兄弟那件事
You talking about the Becerra Brothers?
去新城路上那个
Over New City way?
-是的  -就是他们
- Yeah. - That's them.
算是昨天的新闻
Yesterday's news, literally.
城里有个新来的警长  印第安纳人
There's a new sheriff in town. Indiana boy.
莫纳汉
Monahan.
-莫纳汉  -莫纳汉
- Monahan. - Monahan.
他有很多货可以卖
He's got beaucoup product to move.
-也是美国产的  -好的
- Made in the USA, too. - Oh, all right.
该死  听起来像是我们该认识的人
Well, shoot, that sounds like a guy we should know.
听起来就是我们该认识的家伙
Sounds exactly like a guy we should know.
你们俩在郊区
How much product do you two think you can move
能卖多少货
out in the suburbs?
-一天半磅轻轻松松  -一天一磅也好说
- Half a pound a day, easy. - Pound a day.
卖得好何止这么多  兄弟
Sky's the limit if the glass is clean, bro.
我跟你说  我们有两手
I'm telling you we got something here.
我们有钱  我们有钱
We got the funnel, we got the funnel.
好的
Okay.
确实有点家底
That's some real weight.
我们很认真在谈事  宝贝
It's a serious situation, baby.
我跟莫纳汉联系一下
I'll get in touch with Monahan,
看看能不能谈成
see if I can get the ball rolling.
我们就等着听这话  伙计
That's what we wanted to hear, man.
我来找你就为了这事
That's what I came to you for.
好吧  那就不打扰了  伙计
All right, I will leave you be, man.
祝你愉快  伙计  很高兴见到你  兄弟
Have a good one, man. Great seeing you, bro.
再见  汤米
See you, Tommy.
-你们俩现在成搭档了  -什么
- So now you two partners? - What?
我和鲁塞  我们是兄弟
Me and Ruz, we're buds.
你最好希望如此  因为你在我手上
You better hope so, 'cause now you're on my wing
这事没那么好办
to the bitter end of this thing.
你们真是太搞笑了
You guys are a barrel of laughs.
二十分钟前吧  你告诉亚当你戒毒了
You told Adam you were clean, like, 20 minutes ago.
是的  我之前是戒了
Yeah, I was clean.
二十分钟前
20 minutes ago.
就像一天抽一包烟的人  每二十分钟戒一次
It's like a pack-a-day smoker. Quits every 20 minutes, right?
好了  听着  我没嗑药脑子转不动
All right, look. When I'm not using, my head don't work right.
我反应就不够快  好吗
I can't think fast enough, okay?
如果我在家里乱来什么的也没关系
And that's fine if I'm farting around at home or whatnot,
但是干这个
but in this line of work?
电动滑梯  宝贝  你懂的
Gotta electric slide, baby, you know?
就这样
That's it.
大家都知道冰毒不能
Crystal meth isn't exactly known
激发出人最好的一面  汤米
to bring out the best in people, Tommy.
我完全不认同
I highly disagree.
你看  我们达到目的了
Look, we got what we wanted.
大家都在郁闷什么
What is everyone so glum about?
-汤米  -什么
- Tommy. - What?
如果你想拿到钱  想要抹掉你的记录
If you want your money, you want your record scrubbed,
你不能再嗑药
there's no more dope.
好吧
Fine.
-过来  过来  -他们什么毛病
- Come here, come here. - What's their problem?
回你家去
Just go home to your family.
记住你为什么做这个  好吗
Remember why you're doing this, all right?
喂  你去哪  我要怎么回家
Hey, where you going? How am I supposed to get there?
你走回去
Oh, you take a walk.
走一走  醒醒你那愚蠢的脑子
Take a walk and clear your stupid head.
-怎么了  警长  -你查到什么了
- What's up, Sarge? - What do you got?
印第安纳州警察局确认了
Indiana State Police confirmed the ID of the man
杀害贝塞拉兄弟的凶手的身份
we believe killed the Becerra Brothers.
犯罪嫌疑人  蒂格·罗根
他叫基思·莫纳汉  是个大人物
His name's Keith Monahan. Heavy hitter.
在曼西市那边贩了巨量的冰毒
Sold mountains of crystal meth in Muncie.
他现在来我们这了
He's here now.
印第安纳州方面的情报说他准备在这扎根了
Indiana's intel says he's here to stay.
他们很高兴他现在是我们的问题了
They're pretty happy he's our problem now.
他们发现他和十起谋杀都有关联
They've linked this guy to ten murders,
但莫纳汉狡猾又能算计
but Monahan is smart and he's calculated.
可能知道该往哪藏尸体
Probably knows where to hide the bodies,
所以他总是快他们一步
so he's one step ahead of them all the time.
他们用非法持枪起诉了他两次  但都是轻罪
They got him on two gun charges which are both misdemeanors,
所以他几乎没有犯罪记录
so he's got virtually no record.
所以我们对这起谋杀还是毫无头绪
So we're nowhere on the murders?
好了  我们继续从贩毒方面入手吧
All right, let's keep chasing the drug angle.
我们先用这个把他抓起来
We'll get this son of a bitch off the street that way.
然后再查谋杀案
Then we'll make the murders.
所以呢
So?
罗根·蒂格和莫纳汉接触了
So Logan Teague made contact with Monahan.
我们假装想干票大的
We fronted like we wanted to move some real weight,
所以莫纳汉很感兴趣
so Monahan's pretty interested.
我安排了一次无交易会面  我的线人汤米
I got a dry meet on the books with Tommy, my CI,
罗根和我
Logan, myself.
罗根想看到钱
Logan wants to see money,
他想知道我们够不够格
he wants to know that we're capable,
他想设定规矩和价钱
he wants to set rules and prices,
然后他才会介绍我们和莫纳汉见面
then he'll make the meet with Monahan.
好吧  就这么办
Okay, let's do it.
我了解到你的线人出了点问题
I understand you ran into a little trouble with your CI.
是出了点
Yeah, a bit.
他为任务复吸了  老大
He kind of took one for the team, boss.
我们也得到了我们想要的
And we got what we wanted.
我们不能带着个吸毒的线人
Well, we can't go into a meeting like this
去这样的会面
with a CI high on meth.
把他带到局里关起来
Just bring him in, put him in the box,
在会面之前  我们来帮他戒
we'll keep him clean until the dry meet.
-老大  我不觉得  -把他带来
- Oh, boss, I just don't know - Just bring him in.
好吧
All right.
-你去吗  -嗯  我马上回来
- Wanna go in? - Yeah, I'll be right back.
汤米不在这
Tommy ain't here.
他走了  鲁塞
He's gone, Ruz.
-去哪了  -我不知道
- Gone where? - I never know.
他陷进什么里了
He's into something.
那是什么意思
Well, what does that mean?
通常意味着他会在几天后回来
Usually, it means he'll be back in a few days,
闻着像快死了一样  跪下
smell like death, get on his knees,
求我原谅  一觉睡两天
beg me for forgiveness, sleep 48 hours straight,
然后向我保证他再也不会了
then promise me he'll never do it again.
好吧
Okay.
我会帮你找到他的  我会找到他的  好吗
I'm gonna find him for you. I'm gonna find him, yeah?
快啊  快啊  快快快
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
-什么  在这吗  -对
- What, here? - Yeah.
在十五街和十六街之间的霍曼路
Homan between 15th and 16th.
混蛋
Son of a bitch.
冷静点  你不想伤到他
Keep it together. You don't wanna burn him.
-他是个线人  -我知道我知道
- He's a CI. - I know, I know.
我会用手撕了他
I'm gonna kill him with my bare hands.
找到了
You're good.
该死
Oh, crap.
-你宰了我  -没有
- You ripped me off. - No.
同样的鞋有人比你卖得便宜得多
There's a guy selling the same sneakers for far less
就在独立公园那边
over in Independence Park!
先生  我马上就来
Sir, I'll be with you in a minute.
-我还在接待顾客  -是吗
- I'm just handling a customer. - Yeah?
-伙计  拿上  -你滚开好不好
- So dude, yeah, take - Why don't you get the hell out of here?
我要买这双鞋
I'm trying to buy these shoes.
你要买这双鞋吗
You're trying to buy these shoes?
眼光真不错
That's a very nice choice.
-赶紧滚  -好吧
- Get the hell out of here! - Okay.
-你在干什么  -你欠我一百块
- What are you doing? - You owe me 100 bucks for those, man.
一百块  我马上就要给你五千
100 bucks? I got 5 grand coming your way, man.
你知道卡罗来纳蓝款的
You know what the resale value is
-转卖价值有多高吗  -你有什么毛病
- on Carolina blues, dude? - What's wrong with you?
我像你希望的一样戒毒了
Look, I'm keeping clean like you want.
我戒了  好吗
I am, okay?
我没在吸  虽然很难受  但我在坚持
I am and it hurts and it sucks, but I'm doing it.
但我得糊口啊  伙计
But I gotta make a living, man.
我就是这么赚饭钱的
This is how I put food on my table.
你到底在干什么  伙计
I mean, what are you even doing, man?
你不能在会面之前玩失踪
You can't just disappear right before a meet.
你们两个  都上车
The two of you! Just get in the car.
你感觉怎么样  兄弟
How you feeling, bro?
这里好冷
It's freezing in here.
很遗憾地告诉你这里并不冷
I'm sorry to tell you it's not.
好了  坚持住
All right, well, hang in there.
我去给你拿个毯子  好吗
I'll go get you a blanket, all right?
好了
Okay.
我们在试图拿下一个狡猾且暴力的毒贩
All right, we are trying to take down a smart, violent dealer.
一言不合就杀人的家伙
Guy puts people in the ground they blink the wrong way.
所以我得知道  这家伙到底行吗
So I gotta know: can we do it with this guy?
-行  -不行
- Yeah. - No.
不行
No.
我不是说我们放弃
I'm not saying we surrender.
我只是说我们放了汤米
I'm just saying we cut Tommy lose.
找别的方法去抓莫纳汉
We find another way to get to Monahan.
听着  我懂  我理解
All right, look. I get it, I do.
好的  我懂
All right? I do.
只是你不像我这么了解这人
It's just you do not know this guy like I do.
我知道你们交情很深
I know that you guys go way back.
他为你干了很多活  你们是朋友
He's put in good work for you. You're friends.
但这家伙一团糟  亚当  他就是坏消息
But this guy is a mess, Adam. He's a storm of bad news.
又接到一个双尸案
Just got a call about another double play.
看起来跟莫纳汉有关
Looks like it's connected to Monahan.
让特鲁迪盯着那家伙
Have Trudy keep an eye on that guy.
好的
Yeah.
什么情况
What's the story?
很不幸  还是老生常谈
Unfortunately, it's a familiar one.
死者是雷蒙·圣地亚哥  25岁
DOA is Ramon Santiago. He's 25.
让我猜猜
Let me guess.
西班牙裔  记录在案的帮派成员  冰毒贩子
Hispanic, documented gang banger, crystal meth dealer?
对  被自动步枪枪杀
Yes, sir. Shot and killed by automatic rifle fire
是那边开过来的车
from a vehicle that rolled up on him.
口径0.223弹壳  绿色弹头
Shell casings are .223s. Green tips.
和杀死贝塞拉兄弟的一样
Same rounds that killed the Becerra Brothers.
-另一个受害者呢  -这次是无辜的
- This other victim? - Innocent, this time.
雷蒙的女友  温迪·加西亚
Ramon's girlfriend. Wendy Garcia, 22.
有  曾经有一个三岁儿子
Has a-- had a three-year-old son.
好  让弹道科鉴识这次的子弹
All right, have Ballistics confirm these rounds were fired
和上次杀次贝塞拉兄弟的是否一样
from the same weapon used on the Becerra Brothers.
看死者是否从同一个一次性手机
See if that DOA got any threatening text messages
受到过威胁短信
from the same burner.
我们已经知道了  但是
I mean, we already know but
还是费点力气把两者联系起来
let's do the work to connect the two crimes.
现在有四具尸体了
Body count's up to four now.
莫纳汉想把这事弄得声势浩大  人尽皆知
Monahan's doing this as loud and public as possible.
是的
Yeah.
老大
Boss.
听着  我知道汤米一团糟
Look, I know Tommy's a mess.
他骗人  欺诈  还是个毒贩
He's a liar, he's a cheat, he's a junkie.
你这推销是反其道而行之吗
That's a hell of a sales pitch.
他也是我最好的线人
He's also the best CI I ever had
我觉得我们能挺过去
and I think we can work through this.
眼下
At this point,
我不觉得我们有很多选择
I don't know if we got a lot of choice in the matter.
现在放了他  就是个死胡同了
We cut him loose now, think we're dead in the water.
好吧  很不幸  我觉得你说的对
Yeah, well, unfortunately, I think you're right.
-去办吧  -好的
- Let's get it done. - Yes, sir.
等这案子结束  我们就找人帮你
After this thing's over, we're gonna get you some help.
先考虑把我的钱给我吧
Just worry about getting me my money.
你病了  汤米  没有生计
You're sick, Tommy. No way to live.
是吗  或许吧
Yeah? Well, maybe.
我有可能好起来
There's a chance I get better.
无论结果如何
And however that turns out,
你还是那个来自卡纳里维尔的爱尔兰丑小子
you'll still be an unattractive, Irish prick from Canaryville.
汤米还有力气耍嘴皮子
Tommy's got enough strength to talk smack.
看来还可以
I'd say that's something.
他需要的远不只是耍嘴皮子
He's gonna need more than that.
好了  所以我们的想法是
All right, so we were thinking,
先来两磅
you know, two pounds to start.
你能搞定吗
You get that done?
这就是我擅长的  拓展业务
That's what I do. Generate business.
价格是每磅20
Price'll be 20 per.
20  天呐  这可不便宜啊
20? Damn. I mean, that's pretty steep, man.
和莫纳汉做生意  我劝你别想着讨价还价
With Monahan, I'd encourage you not think of it as a negotiation.
听着  如果我能帮你们牵线搭桥  你们得知道
Look, if I can get this thing set up, you gotta understand.
-如果你们迟到五分钟  他走人  -好
- If you're five minutes late with this guy, he walks. - All right.
你们想改变交易地点  他走人
You try to change the location on him, he walks.
他谁啊  天选之子吗  我们还要亲他的戒指吗
Who's he, the chosen one? We gotta kiss his ring, too?
如果你不喜欢就拉倒
Pull the plug, you don't like it.
-他什么毛病  -他今天过得不好
- What's his problem? - Ah, he's having a rough day.
别管他
Don't worry about him.
我的中介费是一成
My brokerage fee is 10%.
好的  中介费我们和莫纳汉五五分吗
Okay, so then we split that with Monahan?
不不  全是你们出
No. No, that's all on you.
给他钱  我们赶紧走人  老兄
Just pay the man so we can get the hell out of here, man.
好吧  罗根  听着
All right, Logan, look.
第一回做生意  你需要我们先交钱吗
First time out, you need it up front?
我们可以先交钱
We can do it up front.
-你在戒毒吗  -我没事
- Are you dry? - I'm good, bro.
离我远点  老兄
Just step off me, man.
给  爽一把
Here, knock yourself out.
爽一把
Knock yourself out.
见鬼
Damn.
我没事  老兄  不能在这磕嗨
I'm good, man. Not here to get high.
把事儿办了  行吗
Let's just finish this, all right?
-你在戒毒  汤米  -罗根
- You're dry, Tommy. - Logan.
别管他  我们把生意做完
Leave him alone. Let's get this done.
来吧
Go on.
不如你也吸两口  迈克
Why don't you smoke up, too, Mike?
我只卖不吸
I sell it. I don't smoke it.
我说了让你吸两口  迈克
I said smoke up, Mike.
他暴露了  我们去救他
He's made. Let's go get him.
他想继续  我们继续等
He wants to let it play, so we let it play.
你在干什么  别这样啊
What are you doing? I mean, come on.
我们都可以赚一大笔钱
We all stand to make a hell of a lot of money here.
-你在干什么  -对  是这么计划的
- What are you doing? - Yeah, that's the idea, yeah.
你要拿枪指着我吗
And you're gonna pull a piece on me?
我得保护自己
I gotta protect myself.
这行业有很多鬼鬼祟祟的人
There's a lot of sketchy people in this business.
你让我紧张了
You're starting to make me nervous.
你在犯大错  罗根
You're making a very big mistake, Logan.
是吗
Am I?
上
Go!
别挣扎了  罗根  别挣扎了
Stop fighting, Logan. Stop fighting, man.
停下
Stop!
芝加哥警署  芝加哥警署
Chicago PD! Chicago PD!
还有什么
What else you got?
他家那还有冰毒
There's crystal in his place back there.
我们应该带他去检查下  确保他没事
We should get him checked on, make sure he's okay.
好
Yeah.
-你想见我  -对
- You wanted to see me? - Yeah.
到底怎么了
What the hell happened out there?
汤米一团糟  交易没成功
Tommy was a mess. It went south.
可不是嘛
No kidding.
我不得不逮捕那个中间人  我把人关起来了
I had to arrest the broker, so I got him in the box.
我想着策反他  就能抓住莫纳汉了
I'm thinking we flip him, we can get to Monahan that way.
关上门
Shut the door.
怎么了
What's going on?
我收到一个老朋友的电话
I got a call from an old buddy of mine,
13分局的警长
that sergeant in the 13th.
你还记得发生那一切的时候看见过
You happen to recall seeing some crummy liquor store
一家破破烂烂的卖酒店吗
where all this went down?
我们就停在一家卖酒店外面
I mean, we parked right outside of one.
店主在商店旁边的小巷里装了监控
Well, turns out the owner of that store's got a camera in the alley.
说录到了你
Says he's got you on film.
"警察暴力执法"这词现在太流行了
"Police brutality" are the words being tossed around.
你逗我呢  我就掐了他的颈动脉
You gotta be kidding me. I pinned the guy's carotid.
下次我还会这么做
I'd do the exact same thing next time.
老大  我知道这些新规矩
Boss, I know the new rules.
我知道我们在外执勤时所受的限制
I know the limitations when we're out there.
但如果我说我的生命受到威胁  也的确是
But if I say that my life was in danger, which it was,
我相信你
I mean, we're good.
我告诉你  老大  不  那是个暴力现场
I'm telling you, boss, no. This was a violent situation.
-亚当  -我没做错什么
- Adam. - I didn't do anything wrong.
我知道你没做错什么
I know you didn't do anything wrong.
但现在事情不是那么简单了  你懂吗
That's just not the math anymore, you understand?
在这个新的社会秩序下
Bro, in this new world order,
重要的是有渣滓在到处宣传
what matters is that some jerk is shopping around
说你做了错事
the perception that you did something wrong.
就这一点  足以毁了你的事业
That alone is enough to ruin your career,
你懂吗
you understand?
懂
Yeah.
好吧
All right.
你喉咙怎么样了  我的有点干
How's the throat? Mine's a little sore.
这案子你逃不了了  罗根
We got you dead to rights here, Logan.
蓄意贩毒  那是X级重罪
Calculated drug conspiracy. That's a Class X felony.
能判6到30年
You're looking at six to 30.
真是漫长
That's a long time.
我还没说完
We're not actually finished.
你已经有个重罪案底了
You already got a felony on your record,
所以根据判刑法规  还需要加刑
so mandatory extension under sentencing guidelines,
这样就是  我说不好
you're looking at, I don't know,
说的宽松点  大概50年
let's be generous--50 years?
我不会出卖基思·莫纳汉
I ain't flipping on Keith Monahan.
那是死刑  我宁愿坐牢
That's a death sentence. I'd rather be in the joint.
一日三餐
Three squares a day,
洗澡时交几个朋友
couple special friends in the shower.
我没问你的性生活
I didn't ask about your sex life
我也没让你做叛徒
and I didn't ask you to flip.
那你要什么
So what do you want?
你的手机
Your phone.
告诉我密码
Give me the password,
告诉我你和莫纳汉做生意时在哪见面
tell me where you meet Monahan when you do business,
我就帮你谈个好条件
and I will get you a good deal.
我用枪指着警察了  游戏结束
I pulled a piece on a cop. Game over.
我知道  你用枪指着的人是我
I know. You pulled a piece on this cop.
或许我记得的不是这样
Well, maybe I don't remember it that way.
你说什么
What?
细节交给我处理
Let me worry about the details.
如果我们查案顺利  你很快就会出去
Things go well for us, be out of here before you know it.
那么
So.
好了  赶紧  赶紧
All right, come on, man. Come on.
-亚当  -什么事
- Adam. - Yeah.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
装成罗根·蒂格和莫纳汉做买卖
Setting up a buy with Monahan posing as Logan Teague
就像我们在卧底警校学的一样
just like we learned in UC school.
你让罗根遭点小罪
You give Logan a slap on the wrist,
等他出去后  第一件要做的事
the first thing that he does when he gets out,
就是杀了汤米
he pops Tommy.
-不  那不会发生  -会的
- No, that's not gonna happen. - It is gonna happen.
不会  听着  我要关罗根24小时
No, look, I'm gonna hold Logan for 24 hours
然后送到南部
then I'll send him downstate.
等他出来时  如果他要找汤米
By the time he gets out, he's looking for Tommy,
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
他就要去疗养院找了
he's gonna have to search in nursing homes.
你不能扭曲真相  亚当
You can bend the truth in there, Adam,
但我听到你向那男人承诺了
but I heard you give that man your word.
-我不  -你向他保证了
- I don't-- - You promised him something.
等等  等等
Hold on, hold on.
他拿枪指着警察  好吗
He pulled a gun on a cop, all right?
就像他说的  游戏结束
I mean, like he said. Game over.
真见鬼
Good Lord.
如果你觉得这手段肮脏  那你别看
If this too messy for you, look away, please,
因为我晚上能睡得安稳
'cause I will sleep fine tonight.
回复了
Here we go.
好的
Okay.
基思·莫纳汉
卖家谈好了  20每磅  要3磅
下午3点
好戏开始  下午3点
Game on. 3:00 p.m.
现在他指着你和你搭档过去
And now he's expecting you and your partner.
他也会见到我们
Yeah, well, that's what he's gonna get.
你开玩笑吗
You kidding me?
汤米上次的会面都撑不下去
Tommy couldn't make it through that last meeting
-差点功亏一篑  -我会去看看他
- without blowing it up. - I'm gonna check on him.
-亚当  听着  -我会确保他没事
- Adam, listen. - I will make sure he's okay.
一切都会好的  我保证
It's gonna be fine, I promise.
我从没见过情况这么糟  亚当
I never seen it so bad, Adam.
他吃不了东西  喝不了水
He can't keep food down; he can't keep water down.
我当然想让他戒毒
I want him sober, obviously.
我们的情况才刚刚好转
Things were just getting good for us.
但我发誓  我怕他还没戒毒
But I swear to Christ, I'm afraid he's gonna die
就要死了
before he makes it to the other side.
我
I--
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
汤米  别  汤米  别抓了
Tommy, stop. Tommy, stop scratching.
我做不到  史蒂夫
I can't, Steve.
不管你叫什么名字
Whatever your name is supposed to be.
是迈克
It's Mike.
记得吗  迈克  跟单车押韵  迈克
Remember. Mike, bike, Mike.
迈克
Mike.
贩毒的  分销郊区
Drug dealer. Suburbs.
过来  坐起来
Come here. Let's sit you up.
好了  就这样
There you go, all right.
或许下次我们再执行任务
Just, uh, maybe the next time we do this,
你找个更符合你性格的名字
you pick a name that matches your personality more.
比如伊丽莎白
Like Elizabeth.
或阿曼达
Or Amanda.
你坐好  我给你擦擦
You sit tight. I'm gonna clean you up.
我帮你擦干净  好吗
Gonna clean you up, all right?
好了  哥们  过来  哥们
All right, buddy. Come here, bud.
我想让你咬毛巾  好吗
I want you to bite down on this, all right?
慢慢咬  润润嘴  来吧
Just real slow. Wet your whistle a little. Here.
就这样  哥们
Here you go, man.
好样的  乖
Yeah. That's nice.
天呐
God.
我们快抓到人了
Now, we're close.
我去不了了
I'm not gonna make it.
-这样不行  -不
- Not like this. - No.
只有一个方法能到达应许之地
There's only one way to the promised land.
你知道那是什么
You know what that is.
不
No.
可以
Yeah.
-不行  汤米  -可以
- No, Tommy. - Yes.
-不行  -可以
- No. - Yes.
可以
Yes.
你说过是过了普拉斯基街  对吧
You said it's off Pulaski, right?
对  就  再过去点
Yeah, just a... just a little further.
就这里  对对
Here. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
就这里  对  把我在这放下
Here, yeah. Just dump me off right here.
好了  好了
Okay, okay.
好了  去吧
All right. Go, man.
不行
No.
哥们  你不是认真的吧
Bro, you can't be serious right now.
如果这能让你好受点
If it makes you feel any better,
你就当把欠我的球鞋钱
you can just look at it as payment back
还给我好了
for those sneakers you owe me.
什么都不会让我对这事感觉好些
Isn't gonna make me feel better about this.
你需要多少  能让度过今晚
How much you need to make it through the night,
化腐朽为神奇
turn on that magic?
大概两克  60一包
Two grams, maybe. 60 a pop.
好的  好的
Good man, good man.
一切都会好的  好吗
Everything's gonna be okay, all right?
最后都会值得的
It's all gonna be worth it in the end.
-嗯  -好的
- Yeah. - Okay.
亚当和汤米在路上了
Adam and Tommy are on their way.
大家都听着
Everybody listen up.
我们勘察过现场  知道各自的工作
We surveilled the site, we all know our jobs,
但不是我们选的这里
but we didn't pick this spot.
有很多我们不知道的事
There's a lot we don't know
包括对方有多少火力
including how much resistance to expect.
别忘了鲁塞克什么也没带
Don't forget Ruzek's in there naked.
他没有武器
He's got no weapon.
所以我们确保所有人今晚都能活着回去
Let's make sure everyone goes home tonight.
有守卫
We got security.
有两个家伙全副武装
Two guys armed to the teeth.
各方注意  有车来了
Heads up. Coming at us.
好  好戏开始
All right, here we go.
他们在迎接我们的人
They're greeting our party now.
-手张开  -遵命
- Spread. - Yes, sir.
这家伙可真是功能齐全啊
That's a hell of a tricked-out piece, man.
折叠式枪托  消音器
Folding stock, little muzzle suppressor.
怎么  还能帮你做早饭吗
What, it can cook you breakfast, too?
它用什么子弹
What's that thing spit?
绿色弹头  口径0.223
Green tip .223s, bro.
你是街上买来  自己改装的吗
You get the street mod, make it a chopper?
不需要  来的时候就是精装版
No need. Came with a selector.
-全自动  直接开干  -好家伙
- Fully auto, then go home. - Amen to that.
-口径0.223  绿色弹头  全自动  -可能是凶器
- .223s. Green tip, fully auto. - Probably the murder weapon.
数吧
Count it.
我们看到莫纳汉了
We got a positive on Monahan.
我不想让人觉得
I don't mean to give the impression
我想交朋友  因为我不想
that I need to be friends, 'cause I don't.
说的有理
Fair enough.
但我确实需要
But I am in the midst of a...
拓展业务
significant business expansion.
-想找分销的人  -好的
- Looking to move product. - All right.
而不是给自己制造敌人
Not looking to create competition for myself.
罗根说你俩打算去郊区分销
Logan said you two plan to distribute in the suburbs.
没错
That's right.
跟我详细说说
Tell me more about that.
好啊  我们没什么可藏着
Yeah, man. We're an open book.
你想知道什么
You know, tell us what you wanna know.
-我们都告诉你  -你见过那些
- We'll answer any questions you-- - You ever see those birds
站在水牛身上的小鸟吗
that sit on top of them water buffalos?
白色的小鸟  知道吗
White suckers. Know the ones?
我以前想
I used to think,
"你站在水牛身上干什么呢  小鸟"
"What are you doing on top of that buffalo, birdy?"
结果人家是在吃东西呢  没错
Turns out he's having a snack. Yeah.
是真的  我在电视上看到的
It's true. I saw it on TV.
对  鸟吃掉让水牛生病的跳蚤
Yeah, the bird eats the ticks that make the buffalo sick.
这是双赢
It's a win-win for everyone.
水牛健健康康
Buffalo gets a clean bill of health,
小鸟吃得酣畅
bird gets to have a feast.
汤米在发神经吗
Is Tommy geeking out?
是的
He is.
那我是水牛吗  还是鸟
So am I the buffalo? Am I the bird?
你是
You're...
随便什么  老兄
whoever, man.
庄家[贩毒]选
Dealer's choice.
你瞧  我刚玩了个双关
Eh? See what I did there?
但重点是  我们不是对手
But point is we ain't competitors.
那样就太傻了  对吧
We'd be fools, all right?
我们想成为搭档
We want to be partners.
你觉得搭档是什么
What does that look like to you?
-信任  -信任
- Trust. - Trust.
对吧
Right?
所以我会告诉你我们的秘密调料是什么
So I'm gonna tell you what our secret sauce is.
我们要把你的产品  掺入摇头丸  变成超级摇头丸
We're gonna take your product, mix it with X, make super X.
孩子都喜欢
Kids love it.
所以我们瞄准了郊区
That's why we're hitting up the suburbs.
卖给大学生
For the colleges.
草原学院  惠顿学院  州大学
Prairie, Wheaton, State.
我在那些地方都有人  你觉得那里怎么样
I got ins all over the place. What do you think's up there?
听听那孩子说的
Listen to that kid.
一堆孩子
So bunch of kids,
无聊至极  手里又有钱
bored, with a buttload of money,
等人去救他们
just waiting.
等着我们
Waiting for us.
-超级摇头丸  -对
- Super ecstasy? - Yeah.
对  是他想出来的
Yeah, he came up with it.
这家伙真搞笑
Yeah, this guy's funny.
我们弄简单点
Let's keep it simple.
今天做成买卖
We do this deal today.
然后等几天  沉淀一下
Let's let this sit for a minute, simmer.
好
All right.
能瞄准  重复  我能瞄准
Positive. I repeat, we have a positive.
上  上
Move, move.
你怎么说  一周后我们在这见面
What do you say? Meet back here in a week?
一起探索下其他东西
We explore all this other stuff together?
-没问题  -棒极了
- Done. - Yeah, hell yeah, man.
我们会来的
We'll be here.
你没事  你没事
You're good, you're good.
怎么回事  什么情况
What the hell's going on? What the hell is this?
离开这里  汤米
Get out of here, Tommy.
快走  快走
Go now. Go.
跟我说话  伯吉斯
Talk to me, Burgess!
-你还好吗  伯吉斯  -我没事  没事
- Good, Burgess? - I'm good, I'm good!
5021G  发生交火
5021 George. Shots fired.
请注意  有未武装的卧底警察在里面
Be advised, unarmed UC in the middle of it.
-我无法瞄准  -收到
- I don't have a shot. - Copy that.
掩护我  掩护我
Cover me, cover me!
-喂  -芝加哥警署
- Hey! - Chicago PD!
跪下
On your knees.
手放到头后面
Hands behind your head.
我来吧  你们走  我等巡警
I got this--you guys go. I'll wait for patrol.
警察  站住
Police, stop!
芝加哥警署  转过身
Chicago PD! Turn around!
转身  莫纳汉  别逃了
Turn around, Monahan! Stop moving!
把枪放下
Put the gun down.
我觉得不可能
Yeah, I don't think I will.
把枪放下  莫纳汉
Put the gun down, Monahan.
你完蛋了  无处可逃了
This thing's over. There's nowhere to go.
把枪放下
Put it down.
完了吗
Is it over?
莫纳汉  你如果再继续拿枪指着我朋友
Monahan, you don't stop pointing that gun at my friend,
我发誓  我会开枪打死你
I swear to God, I will drop you!
放下枪
Put it down!
Put it down.
你不会打我
You ain't gonna shoot me.
放下枪
Put it down.
放下
Put it--
天呐
God!
鲁塞  鲁塞
Ruz, Ruz.
汤米  汤米
Tommy, Tommy.
听着  我需要你把手
Listen, man. I need you to take your hands,
紧紧地按在这里  好吗
I need you to put 'em right there, okay?
-按住了  好吗  -好
- Hold down, all right? - Sure...
-我们会送你去医院  -汤米
- We'll get you all covered up. - Tommy!
警长  他在东边
Sarge, we found him at the east end!
有交火  嫌犯死了  鲁塞没事
Shots fired, offender down! Ruz is okay!
好吗  把眼睛睁开
All right? Just keep your eyes open.
-抱歉  抱歉  -收到
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry. - Copy that.
别再说"抱歉"了
Stop saying, "I'm sorry."
你做得很好  不是你的错
You did good. Not your fault.
好了  好了
There you go, there you go.
我来吧
I got him.
-谢谢  -客气
- Thank you. - Yeah.
你要把眼睛睁开  好吗
I need you to keep your eyes open, eh?
我需要你一直跟我说话  好吗
I need you to keep talking to me, all right?
眼睛睁开
Hey, keep your eyes open.
5021D  有人受伤  胸口枪伤
5021 David, we got a man down, GSW to the chest.
你得把眼睛睁开
You gotta keep your eyes open
为了伊莎贝尔和你家人  好吗
for Isabel and your family, right?
你得回到他们身边
You gotta go home to 'em now,
享受你劳动的果实
enjoy the fruits of your labor.
好吗  汤米
Yeah? Tommy.
我的  我的卧底名字叫什么
Hey, what's-- hey, what's my undercover name?
伊丽莎白
Elizabeth.
没错  就是伊丽莎白
Yeah, that's right. Elizabeth it is.
你把眼睛睁开
You keep those eyes open.
你干得很好  哥们  干得很好
You did good, bro. You did good.
你坚持住  汤米  汤米  坚持住
You stay with me, Tommy. Tommy, you stay with me.
我搞砸了
I screwed up.
犹豫了
Hesitated.
我头脑里有好多声音
I just had all these voices in my head.
规则和
You know, rules and...
不是客观的对错  而是别人眼中的对错
not right or wrong, the perception of right or wrong,
那些乱七八糟的  让我失了判断
and all that crap and I don't have my piece.
拿着一把杀了四个人的步枪
Carrying a rifle that's used to murder four people.
这家伙不是拿枪指着我
This guy's not pointing the gun at me,
而是指着汤米
he's pointing a gun at Tommy.
那我又知道什么呢
And so what the hell do I know?
我知道什么
What do I know?
我再也不能相信我的本能了
Can't trust my instincts anymore.
我觉得我那一枪开得很合法
And I think I had a lawful shoot out there.
-没错  -我知道
- You did. - I know.
我知道
I know.
但我却犹豫了  而且
Yet I hesitated and I...
直到他枪击了我朋友  我才开枪
didn't pull the trigger until after he shot my friend.
听着  亚当
Look, Adam.
亚当
Adam.
我们在面对一系列新的规矩
I mean, we're running point on a whole new thing here.
你要把他们在这里写的规矩
You're taking all these new rules they're writing in here,
带到外面混乱的世界去执行
taking them into the chaos out there.
这一点不容易
It's not gonna be easy.
尤其是当你只有半秒钟决定
Not when you got, what, half a second to decide
该开枪打死这个人  救那个人的情况下
whether to take one guy's life in order to save another?
但我告诉你  正义
Tell you one thing, right...
正义依旧是正义  亚当
I mean, right is still right, Adam.
我想我们只能
I think we're all gonna be
在黑暗中摸索一阵了
groping around in the dark for a while.
是啊
Yeah.
知道吗
You know?
至少我们能一起摸索
Least we'll be doing it together, man.